Guide to the New York Foundation For the Arts (NYFA) Records MSS.515
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII. Other NYFA Programs, 1970-2010; 45 linear feet in 45 record cartons
  - Subseries I. New York-Israel Cultural Cooperation Commission, 1998-2004; 7 linear feet
    - The Center for Contemporary Art, 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - FJC: A Foundation of Philanthropic Funds, 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Buffalo Arts Studio, 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - ApexArt Curatorial Program, 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - City Parks Foundation, 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - International Committee for Dance Library of Israel, Inc., 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - International Vocal Arts Institute, Inc., 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - The Jewish Community Center in Manhattan, Inc., 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - The Jerusalem Foundation, Inc., 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Arts in General, Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Art Studios of Wester New York/dba Buffalo Arts Studio, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - ApexArt Curatorial Program, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Bronx River Art Center Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - The Brooklyn Jewish Film Festival, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - College of Staten Island, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Dancing in the Streets, Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Eastern School of Music, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Haleakala, Inc. dba The Kitchen, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - The Jewish Museum, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Oswego College Foundation, Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Queens Museum of Art, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Trustees of Hamilton College, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Visual Studies Workshop, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Yeshiva University Museum, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - NYICCC Correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 96, Folder 28)
    - NYICCC Correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 96, Folder 29)
    - NYICCC Correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 96, Folder 30)
    - Celebrate Brooklyn! Performing Arts Festival, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 31)
    - North American Jewish Choral Festival, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 32)
    - Grant Applications (Blank), 2002 (Box 96, Folder 33)
    - Minister Counselor Administrative Affairs Letter, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 34)
    - Heratiya Museum, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 35)
    - NYICCC Press List, Correspondence, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 36)
    - NYICCC: Art in General, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 37)
    - NYICCC Pregame Preliminary Application, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 38)
    - NYICCC Contact Sheet, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 39)
    - NYICCC Correspondence: NYSCA! List of Museums in NYS, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 40)
    - NYICCC Presenters List, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 41)
    - NYICCC Correspondence, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 42)
    - NYICCC Chairman's Report, 2001 (Box 96, Folder 43)
    - NYICCC Meeting Minutes, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 44)
    - NYICCC Agendas, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 45)
    - NYICC Faxes to French Institute Alliance Française, 2001 (Box 96, Folder 46)
    - NYICCC FY02 Budget Ledger, 2001-2002 (Box 96, Folder 47)
    - NYICCC Chairman's Correspondence, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 48)
    - NYICCC Administration, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 49)
    - NYICCC Letter of Agreement with ESDC, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 50)
    - NYICCC Disbursements, 1999-2001 (Box 96, Folder 51)
    - NYICCC Old Budget Information, 1999-2001 (Box 96, Folder 52)
    - NYICCC Funding Balance Sheet, 2003 (Box 96, Folder 53)
  - Subseries J. Arts and Technology, 1995-2002; 9 linear feet
    The Arts and Technology Programs consists of NYFA program information, development papers for technology workshops and conferences, attendee lists for workshops and conferences, survey findings and research notes on technology, technology conference program information and lists, and technology grant application materials.
    This series begins with the folder containing Arts and Technology Program survey information and follows with programs (workshops, conferences, grant opportunities) developed by NYFA in response to artists' consensus regarding implementation of technology into the arts. Workshops are arranged chronologically. Grant applications are arranged chronologically and alphabetically.
    - State of the Digital Arts: A Survey, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - ArtsWire SpiderSchool: Developing Projects for the Internet and Web, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - ArtsWire SpiderSchool: "Digital Literacy", 1997 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - ArtsWire Workshops Evaluations and Finance Reports, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - ArtsWire Technology Workshops Leaders' Contracts, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Statewide Art and Technology Workshops - Evaluation of Phase 1, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Workshop Hosts - Potential Lists, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Buffalo, ArtsWire Technology Workshop, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Chenango and Capitol Region, ArtsWire Technology Workshop, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - NYSCA/Presenting Organizations, ArtsWire Technology Workshop, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Oneonta, Artswire Technology Workshop, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Poughkeepsie, ArtsWire Technology Workshop, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Rockland, ArtsWire Technology Workshop, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Rochester, ArtsWire Technology Workshop, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Syracuse, ArtsWire Technology Workshop, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Westchester, ArtsWire Technology Workshop, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Statewide Gatherings, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - ArtsWire New Trainer Orientation, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - 171 Cedar Street Arts Center, ArtsWire Technology Workshop, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Ithaca, The Community School of Music and Art, ArtsWire Technology Workshop, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Arts Council for the Northern Adirondacks, ArtsWire Technology Workshop, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Delaware Valley Arts Alliance, ArtsWire Technology Workshop, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Dutchess County, ArtsWire Technology Workshop, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - RCCA/Broome County/Clinton,Pittsburgh/Hamilton-NYSCA Presenting, ArtsWire Technology Workshop, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Spring Contacts, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - ArtsWire Spider School: "Technology Planning", 1999 (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - ArtsWire Spider School: "Digital Literacy", 1999 (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - Registration for NYFA Technology Planning Workshop, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - NYFA Arts and Technology Program Information, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - ArtsWire SpiderSchool: Technology Planning for Arts Organizations Workshop, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Account and Expenses, 1998-1999 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - ArtsWire Technology Workshop: Contractor Agreements and Invoices, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - ArtsWire Technology Workshop: Expenses, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - ArtsWire Technology Workshop: Spring Expenses, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - ArtsWire Technology Workshop Trainers Orientation, Contractor Agreements, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Supplies, Hospitality, Postage and Shipping, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Budget and Expenses, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Governor's Conference on Arts and Technology, CIRCUITS@NYS, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Post-NYSCA Technology Conference, TIIAP Consultant Agreements and Invoices, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Fax Lists and Correspondence, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Palisades Center Expenses, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Kick Off Event Expenses, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Personnel Expenses, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Refunds/Cancellations, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Artists Fees and Expenses, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Travel Expenses (Consultants, Presenters, Artists), 1998 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Printint, Postage, Supplies Expenses, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Website and Broadcasting/Pre-Conference Technical Assistance, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Revenue, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Personnel Expenses, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - CIRCUITS@NYS: Program Description, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Personnel Expenses, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Advertising, Printing, Supplies Expenses, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Travel Expenses, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Changes in the database, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Registration Information and Requests, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Brochure Development Materials, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Complete Applications (Staff/Comp), 1998 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Complete Applications, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Complete Applications, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Complete Applications, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Complete Applications, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Waitlist Applications, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Consultants Expenses, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - The Arts in a Digital Age, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - The Arts in a Digital Age, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Independent Media Arts Preservation, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Electronic Arts Intermix, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Upper Catskills Community Council of the Arts, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - New York Folklore Society, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - José Limon Dance Foundation, Inc., 1999 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Jamaica Center for Arts and Living, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Harvestworks Digital Media Arts, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Film/Video Arts, Inc., 1999 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Experimental Television Center Ltd., 1999 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Dance Notation Bureau, Inc., 1999 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Center for Exploratory and Perceptual Art (CEPA), 1999 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Brooklyn Information and Culture, Inc., 1999 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Bronx Council on the Arts, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Grant Recipients, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - 1687, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - 3-Legged Dog, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - ABC No Rio, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Albany Symphony Orchestra, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Alfred Univerity, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Alliance of New York State Arts Council, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Access to the Arts, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - The Acting Company, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Albany Institute of History and Art, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Albany/Schnectady League of Arts, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - The Alliance of Resident Theatres/New York, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - American Composers Orchestra, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - American Museum of the Moving Image, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - American Music Center, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Arm-of-the-Sea Productions, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Arnot Art Museum, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Ars Nova Musicians Chamber Orchestra, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Art2Facts, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Arts and Cultural Council for Greater Rochester, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Arts Council for Wyoming County, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Arts for Art, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Arts Horizons, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Art in Context Center for Communications, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Art Lab, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Artsgenesis, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Asian American Arts Alliance, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Asian American Arts Centre, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - Asian American Writers' Workshop, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - Association of Hispanic Arts, Inc. (AHA), 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - Association of Teaching Artists, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - Babylon Citizens Council on the Arts, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - Ballet Hispanico of New York, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - Ballet Hispanico of New York, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 48)
    - Bardovan 1869 Opera House, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 49)
    - Bard College, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 50)
    - Belmont Italian American Playhouse, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 51)
    - BlackSpectrum Theatre Company, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 52)
    - Boswell Museum, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 53)
    - Bronx Council on the Arts, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 54)
    - The Bronx Museum of the Arts, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 55)
    - Bronx River Art Center and Gallery, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 56)
    - Brooklyn Historical Society, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 57)
    - Brooklyn Information and Culture, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 58)
    - Brookside, Saratoga County Historical Society, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 59)
    - Buffalo Inner City Ballet Company, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 60)
    - Buffalo Media Resources, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 61)
    - Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra Society, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 62)
    - Burchfield-Penney Art Center, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 63)
    - The Builders Association, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 64)
    - Carnegie Art Center/Tonawandas' Council on the Arts, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 65)
    - Center for Exploratory and Perceptual Art (CEPA), 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 66)
    - The Center for Photography at Woodstock, Inc. (CPW), 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 67)
    - Center for Traditional Music and Dance, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 68)
    - Chinese Theatre Workshop, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 69)
    - Circum-Arts Foundation, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 70)
    - City College-Institute for Research on the African Diaspora in the Americas and Caribbean, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 71)
    - City Lore, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 72)
    - Community Arts Partnership of Tompkins County, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 73)
    - Composers Collaboration, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 74)
    - Composers Recordings, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 75)
    - Concert Artists Guild, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 76)
    - The Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 77)
    - The Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 78)
    - Cornell Institute for Digital Collections, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 79)
    - Craft Alliance of New York State, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 80)
    - Craft Alliance of New York State, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 81)
    - Creative Time, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 82)
    - CSC Repertory Ltd., Classic Stage Company, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 83)
    - Dance Notation Bureau, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 84)
    - Dance Theater Workshop, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 85)
    - Das Puppenspiel Puppet Theater, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 86)
    - Delaware County Historical Association, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 87)
    - Downtown Community Television Center, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Eastside Neighbors In Partnership (ENIP), 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Educational Video Center (EVC), 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Elaine Kaufman Cultural Center/Lucy Moses School for Music and Dance, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Eldridge Street Project, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Arts Intermix, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - En Foco, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - The EOS Orchestra, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - The Ensemble Studio Theatre, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - ES Experimental Intermediate Foundation, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Experimental Television Center Ltd., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Eyebeam Atelier, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Fiji Theater, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Film/Video Arts, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Spanish Dance Arts Company, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Flushing Council on Culture and the Arts, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Film/Video Arts (FVA), 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Foundation for Independent Video and Film, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Franklin Furnace Archive Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Gallery Association of New York State, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Genesee-Orleans Regional Arts Council, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - The Gertrude Stein Repertory Theatre, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Gowanus Arts Exchange, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Haleakala, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Hallwalls, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - HarlemLive, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Harlem Textile Works, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Harvestworks, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Historic Hudson Valley, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Hoff. Barthelson Music School, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Home for Contemporary Theatre and Art DBA HERE, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - The House Foundation for the Arts, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Hudson Guild, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Hudson Valley Children's Museum, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Hudson Valley Shakespeare Festival, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Hudson Valley Film and Video Office, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Huntington Arts Council, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - iEAR Studios, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - International Agency for Minority Artist Affairs, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Jamaica Center for Arts and Learning, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Jazz Forum Arts, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - Jewish Repertory Theatre, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - José Limon Dance Foundation, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - The Landmark Society of Western New York, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 44)
    - Lehman College Art Gallery, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 45)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 46)
    - Locust Street Neighborhood Art Classes, Inc. (FKA Molly Olga), 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 47)
    - Lower East Side Printshop, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 48)
    - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 49)
    - Mabou Mines Development Foundation, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 50)
    - Manhattan Theatre Club, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 51)
    - Maverick Concerns, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 52)
    - Media Alliance, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 53)
    - The Michael J. Quill Irish Cultural and Sports Centre, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 54)
    - The MicroMuseum aka Promote Art Works, Inc. (PAWI), 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 55)
    - Millenium Film Workshop, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 56)
    - Mohonik Preserve, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 57)
    - Movement Research, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 58)
    - Movement Research, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 59)
    - Museum of Chinese in the Americas, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 60)
    - The Museum at Stony Brook, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 61)
    - National Choral Council/The National Chorale, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 62)
    - National Museum of Racing, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 63)
    - National Museum of the American Indian, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 64)
    - The Network of Cultural Centers of Color, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 65)
    - New Radio and Performing Arts, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 66)
    - The New York Festival of Song, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 67)
    - New York Folklore Society, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 68)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 69)
    - The New York Lesbian and Gay Experimental Film/Video Festival, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 70)
    - Niagara Council of the Arts, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 71)
    - Northern Westchester Center for the Arts, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 72)
    - Oswego Opera Theatre, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 73)
    - One Seventy One Cedar, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 74)
    - Paper Tiger Television, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 75)
    - Paramount Center for the Arts, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 76)
    - The Pauline Oliveros Foundation, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 77)
    - Performance Space 122, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 78)
    - Performance Zone, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 79)
    - Pine Bush Area Arts Council, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 80)
    - Poetry Society of America, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 81)
    - Queens Council on the Arts, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 82)
    - Queens Museum of Art, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 83)
    - Regional Council of Historical Agencies, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 84)
    - Rejoicensemble, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 85)
    - REPOHistory, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 86)
    - Rochester Philharmonic Orchestra, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 87)
    - The Rockwell Museum, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 88)
    - Roulette Intermedium, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - The Roxbury Arts Group, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Sculpture Space, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Smack Mellon Studios, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - South Street Seaport Museum, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - The St. Ann Center for Restoration and the Arts, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Studio Theatre School, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Teachers and Writers Collaborative, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Teatro Circulo Ltd., 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Ten Penny Players, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Theatre By the Blind Corp., 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Theatre Communications Group, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Third World Newsreel/Camera News, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Thread Waxing Space, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Ticonderoga Festival Guild, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Time and Space Limited Theater Company, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Transart and Cultural Services, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Union Learning Center, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - University of Rocheser/Memorial Art Gallery, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Visual Studies Workshop, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Volunteer Lawyers for the Arts, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Wayne County Council for the Arts, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - White Columns, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Westchester Philharmonic, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - The Wooster Group, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Writers and Books, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - The Writers Room, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - X Art Foundation, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Young Audiences/New York, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - 1687, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - 171 Cedar Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Albany/Schnectady League of Arts, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Alliance of New York State Arts Organizations (ANYSAO), 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - American Composers Orchestra, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - American Music Center, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Arts Council in Buffalo and Erie County, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Arts and Culture for Oswego County, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Arts and Cultural Council for Greater Rochester, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - The Bronx Museum of the Arts, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 42)
    - Brooklyn Conservatory of Music, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 43)
    - Brooklyn Museum of Art, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 44)